Previously on Hostages...
前情提要
Who the hell are you?
你到底是谁
I know you're related to Nina Carlisle.
我知道你和Nina Carlisle 有血缘关系
Trust me,you don't want to get involved in this.
相信我 你不应该介入此事
You're Kate Renner. Nina's mother.
你就是Kate Renner Nina的母亲
- Glad you could make it. - What do you want?
- 很高兴你能来 - 你想干什么
I need a friend inside Duncan's operation.
我想在Duncan的团队内有个朋友
You're talking to the wrong girl.
你找错人了
Okay,a spy.
好吧 内应
What are you offering?
你出什么价
Just because we're sleeping together,you do not get to treat me like your secretary.
你不能因为我们上过床 就把我当秘书使唤
- OTI has to end. - You want to dismantle it?
- 全信行动必须终止 - 你想取消项目?
I want to expose it.
我想公诸于世
OTI is important. Don't give this bastard a chance to take that away from you.
全信行动很重要 别让那混蛋从你手上夺走
Do we really want to bet the future of this country on Dr. Sanders?
真的要把国家的未来 压在Sanders医生身上?
Or Duncan Carlisle?
或是Duncan Carlisle?
They tried and failed. Why should we believe they'll pull it off this time?
他们失败过 我们凭啥相信这次会成功
Kramer took a photo of a guy talking to the Secret Service agent.
Kramer拍了照片 那个跟特勤局探员交谈的人
You got a name?
知道身份吗
Robert Harper. Former Army Ranger and decorated sniper.
Robert Harper 退役游骑兵 授勋的狙击手
Sniper?
狙击手?
Did you kill him?
你杀死他了吗
I went to his apartment,but he wasn't there.
我去过他的公寓 他不在
He's on a plane to New York City right now.
他在去纽约的飞机上
If he's trying to kill you,why is he on his way to New York?
如果要杀你 为何要去纽约
Because I'm not the target.
因为我不是目标
The President is.
总统才是
He's scheduled to be in New York all day tomorrow.
明天他都在纽约
If they succeed,Nina dies.
如果行刺成功 Nina就会死
Then we need to get there first.
我们要先下手为强
The president is gonna be in New York today.
总统明天会在纽约
Another team is being assembled to take him out while he's there.
有另一队人计划在此期间行刺总统
- We have to stop them. - Hold up there.
- 我们要阻止他们 - 等等
- How exactly is that on us? - Target goes away,our payday goes away.
- 为何要这样做 - 目标死了 我们的报酬也没了
- Our deal is with you. - Your deal is to complete the mission.
- 我们是跟你交易的 - 你要完成任务才能拿钱
We can't do that if somebody beats us to the punch.
如果其他人抢先动手 我们就没机会
So how do we do it?
那现在要怎办
None of this is your fault.
你没做错什么
You didn't ask for this,and you don't deserve it.
这不是你的责任 你也不应承受这一切
But now that we're here,we have to do everything we can to make the right decisions.
但事已至此 我们要尽力做正确的决定
We shouldn't be helping these people.
我们不该帮这些人
- What about when we don't have a choice? - You always have a choice.
- 如果我们没有选择? - 总会有选择的
- Mom says we need to cooperate. - Cooperate? Yeah.
- 妈说我们要合作 - 合作? 是的
Not collaborate.
但不是勾结
- What does that mean? - It means that
- 你什么意思 - 就是说
when this is over I want you to be able to look at yourselves in the mirror.
当此事过去 你能坦然面对自己的良心
I don't want to let them turn you into something that you're not.
我不能坐视你们变成另一个人
They made you lie to Boyd's father about his death.
他们让你对Boyd的父亲隐瞒真相
And they made you come up with a phony alibi for Kramer.
他们还让你帮Kramer作伪证
Where is this gonna end?
这些事何时才会结束
- With Mom killing the president. - I don't accept that.
- 等妈杀掉总统之后 - 我不能接受
And if it does,then...
如果真是这样 那就...
If it does,then what?
如果真是这样 怎样?
I don't want this family to lose its way.
我不想这个家变得面目全非
Everybody on your feet. You're coming with us.
大家都起来 跟我来
Let's go. Move! Get up!
快点 起来
Move! Up!
快点
TEXT MESSAGE ******
在金利街5305号 东南边的仓库见面
I'm glad you called.
很高兴你联系我
So all I gotta do is tell you what's going on?
我只需要告诉你情况进展?
Like I said last night,all I need is information.
我昨晚说过 我只需要情报
Where people are,what they're doing.
你们在哪里 做什么
You're my eyes and ears.
你是我的耳目
I want to know if Duncan's sticking to the plan,that he's watching the Sanders family 24/7.
Duncan是否按计划行事 全天候监视Sanders一家
And,if he's not,call me.
如果没有 通知我
How do I know you're gonna deliver on your end of this?
你怎么保证事成后信守承诺
Two Canadian passports. One for you,one for your son.
两本加拿大护照 你和你儿子
And what about the cash?
现金呢?
Keep it. Consider it a gesture of good faith.
拿着吧 就当是诚意金
I'll give you the rest when this is all over.
剩下的事成后给你
10 grand is nothing to the people I'm working for.
一万元对我老板来说不算什么
They just wanna know what's going on with Duncan.
他们只想知道Duncan的行踪
It's an insurance policy. That's all.
以防万一 没别的意思
You made the right decision.
你做得很对
Trust me. It's much better than the alternative.
相信我 这比另一个选择好得多
I've gotta get back.
我要回去了
Sit down.
坐下
Windows are nailed shut. Door will be locked from the outside.
窗户钉死了 门也从外面锁上
You're gonna be in here for a while,so make yourselves comfortable.
你们要在这里待一段时间 尽量放松点
What's going on?
怎么回事
None of you are leaving the house today.
今天你们都不能离开房子
I've sent Sandrine and Kramer ahead to start surveillance on this church.
我让Sandrine和Kramer 提前去监视这间教堂
And to look for the sharp shooter we saw yesterday,Robert Harper.
同时寻找昨天见到的狙击手 Robert Harper
You and I are gonna try and narrow the search.
我和你要缩窄搜索范围
What do you know about the president's schedule?
你对总统的行程了解多少?
Off the record trips are low-profile. The goal is to avoid being noticed.
非官方出行都很低调 会尽量避人耳目
Kincaid will be in an unmarked SUV,without the usual number of Secret Service agents.
Kincaid会坐无标记的车辆 随行人员也少很多
They'll most likely bring him through this back alley,here.
他们可能会从后巷进来 这里
Why don't we simply call in a bomb threat?
为何不搞个炸弹威胁?
- Make them divert his plans. - If we do anything to make
- 让他们取消行程 - 如果这样做
Kincaid's security detail suspect there's a plot against him,protocol dictates they completely change his itinerary.
安全部门会认为有人对总统不利 所有事情都会重新评估
That would include the location of his surgery,and the staff performing.
包括手术医院和主刀医生
We need to find this other hit team and take them out,without anybody knowing it happened.
我们要不引起注意地 干掉另一队人
Hello,it's Burton. Am I all set on that flight to Madrid?
你好 我是Burton 去马德里的机票订好了吗?
Two tickets.
两张
For myself,and for my granddaughter.
我和我孙女
Okay. Let me know as soon as possible.
好的 尽快通知我
- Kate. - Hello,Burton.
- Kate - 你好 Burton
Come inside.
进来
What are you doing here? I thought we had an arrangement.
你过来做什么? 我们有过约定的
I know. I'm sorry.
我知道 对不起
You shouldn't be here,ever.
你不应该出现 永远
- A woman came to see me. - Yes?
- 有个女人来找过我 - 是的
- Dr. Sanders. - Why didn't you tell me Nina was sick?
- Sanders医生 - 你为何不告诉我Nina病了
Because...
因为...
we always said you would move on with your life and put Nina behind you.
我们说过你该重新开始 忘了Nina的事
- Why burden you with her health problems? - She's still my daughter.
- 为何要为她的健康问题去打扰你 - 她始终是我的女儿
- I had a right to know. - Is that why you're here,Kate?
- 我有权知道 - 这是你来此的目的 Kate?
I'm here because I want to tell my story.
我过来 是希望将我的故事讲出来
I want to expose Kincaid.
我要揭露Kincaid的丑事
Things in place in New York?
纽约的事安排好了吗
I just spoke to the team leader.
我刚和领队谈过
They landed last night. They're assembling now.
他们昨晚到了 正在部署
- Everything's a go. - Good.
- 一切就绪 - 很好
Good. What about the girl? She accept your offer?
那个女孩怎样 接受你的条件吗
She's in.
她同意了
Okay. Stay in contact with her throughout the day.
好的 今天跟她保持联系
The minute we're done in New York,we need to be ready to move on Duncan and his team.
纽约的任务一完成 就干掉Duncan和他的小队
- I understand. - Duncan needs to go first.
- 明白 - 先除掉Duncan
Then the others.
再解决其他人
What about the Sanders family?
Sanders一家怎么办
Make it a murder-suicide.
伪造成家庭伦常惨案
A weapon will be left in the father's hand,with a note,bemoaning his financial issues and marital problems.
枪放在丈夫手里 再留言 称受困于财务状况和婚姻关系
It's never pleasant taking out innocent civilians,but we don't have a choice.
杀害无辜平民很让人难受 但我们别无选择
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET-   定风波
-=伊甸园美剧 http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站 http://ytet.org=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
Hostages Season 01 Episode 11
人质 第一季 第11集
If I were them,I'd be looking to get some elevation.
如果是我 我会寻找制高点
Only a few structures in the vicinity have the heightened position to give you an angle on that alley.
只有少量建筑有足够高度 看到小巷里面
The sniper team will be looking for a quick exit to a major thoroughfare.
狙击小队还要考虑 能快速撤离到主干道
I only see three buildings that fit the bill.
只有三栋楼符合条件
- One. Two. Three. - Yeah.
- 一 二 三 - 对
- Which one will they use? - Don't know yet,
- 他们会选择哪一栋 - 还不清楚
but a sniper's only as good as his spotter,and a spotter is only as good as his vantage point.
但狙击手需要好的观测员 而观测员要占据地利
We need more information.
我们需要更多信息
We don't have enough time to do an internal recon in three high-rise buildings.
我们没足够时间 对三栋楼做内部调查
You're right.
你说得对
We need the blueprints for each building with complete specifications.
我们需要每栋楼详细的蓝图
How are we gonna get those?
怎样可以搞到图纸?
After that doctor left,I started thinking about all those secrets I kept,for so long.
那个医生走后 我想及保守多年的秘密
I got angry.
我感到愤怒
I've told my husband everything.
我都告诉我丈夫了
Kate,we had a deal.
Kate 我们说好的
And I can only imagine how difficult
我知道你过得很艰难
- these past years... - Decades!
- 过去的几年... - 是几十年
...decades have been for you,but Kincaid's a dangerous man. I don't need to tell you that.
几十年也过来了 Kincaid很危险 你知道的
He's a lot more powerful than he was 35 years ago.
他的权势比35年前大得多
I'll take my chances.
我想试试
I think I'm old enough to make that decision for myself.
我已经不是不谙世事的小姑娘
What about for Nina?
那Nina怎么办
She's at risk as well.
她也会有危险
Nina has terminal leukemia.
Nina现在白血病晚期
According to that doctor,there's no match for her bone marrow,right?
据那个医生所说 没有找到匹配的骨髓 对吗?
I want my daughter to know the truth before she dies.
我想让我女儿死前得知真相
We haven't given up.
我们还没有放弃
I need something from you.
我要你帮我找点东西
I want schematics on three buildings in New York.
我要纽约三栋大楼的图纸
- Schematics? What for? - Your firm has a password
- 图纸? 做什么 - 你的公司能登入数据库
for the property clerk's database in most major cities,correct?
查阅大多数城市的房产物业 对吗?
Yeah,they do,but I can't access them whenever I want.
是的 但我也需要授权
- It's not that simple. - Why do you need the specs?
- 没那么简单 - 你要图纸做什么
It's important to all of us.
这对我们很重要
Well,I'm sorry. There are a lot of regulations.
抱歉 公司规矩很多
Privacy,security restrictions.
私隐条例 安保守则
Can't help you.
没法帮你
Can't? Or won't?
是不能还是不想
Both.
都是
You still haven't learned anything,Brian.
你还没吸取教训 Brian
On your feet. Let's go.
站起来 我们走
- Mom!
- 妈
Where are you taking her?
你带她去哪里
Mom!
妈
You wanted to tell me something?
你有话要对我说?
I think I can get the schematics you need.
我想我可以拿到你要的图纸
- Good. - But I want to know.
- 很好 - 但我要知道
What's it for? I know the president is in New York today.
用来做什么 我知道总统今天在纽约
What are... Are you gonna kill him?
你...想杀了他吗?
No. I'm gonna save him.
不 我想救他
But I need those specs,Ellen. Soon.
但我需要图纸 Ellen 尽快
Here.
给你
If I fail in New York,Ellen,if you hear that the president has been killed,
如果我在纽约失败了 你得知总统被杀
then you need to go upstairs,free your family,and get the hell out of here. Fast.
上楼放了你的家人 尽快离开此地
- Do you understand what I'm telling you? - Yes.
- 明白我意思吗? - 是的
I know you'll never believe me,but...
我知道你不相信我 但是...
I wish you never had to be involved.
我真心不想将你牵连进来
Thank you for coming.
感谢你过来
I was really surprised that you called me.
我很惊讶你打电话给我
I thought you guys were in Montreal? Why isn't Brian back at the office?
我以为你们在蒙特利尔 为何Brian不上班
Well,that's why I'm here. Brian...
这是我找你的原因 Brian...
- got himself into some financial trouble. - I don't understand.
- 他有财务困难 - 我不明白
Well,the company is heavily leveraged. Deeply,deeply in debt.
事实上公司负债严重
Then about six months ago,he borrowed a large sum of money from some people.
六个月前 他借了一大笔钱
The wrong people. And then when he couldn't pay them back
那些坏人 当他无法还债
they,they threatened to hurt our family.
他们威胁要伤害我们一家
What?
什么?
That's why he dropped the passports off that day.
所以那天他让你送护照
We thought we had to get out of the country in a hurry.
我们想设法逃到国外
Why didn't Brian say anything to me?
为何Brian从未提起此事
Well,I don't think he wanted to get you involved.
可能他不希望牵连你
He's out of town right now,but he really needs your help.
他现在不在城里 但他真的需要你帮忙
We need your help.
我们需要你的帮助
I don't blame you for anything that happened.
我不会为你们的事责怪你
All I care about right now is protecting my family.
我现在只想保护家人
Why don't you go to the police?
为什么不报警
That would make it even worse. I mean,these people are really dangerous.
那只会更糟 那些人真的很危险
- They would hurt our kids. - Right.
- 他们会伤害我的孩子 - 好吧
Well,what do you need from me?
你想要我做什么
Your company access code.
你公司的密码
We need the schematics for three buildings in New York.
我们需要纽约三栋大楼的图纸
For the business deal,just to help Brian dig himself out of this mess.
这是交易内容 为了帮Brian摆脱困境
This is Nina's sixth birthday party.
这是Nina十六岁的生日会
And why does the boy standing next to her have frosting all over his face?
为何她旁边的男孩满脸糖霜
Oh,that's Alex. He lived two doors down. Bit of a bully.
那是Alex 就住在附近 是个小霸王
Alex made the mistake of trying to take Nina's cupcake,and she shoved it in his face.
Alex想抢Nina的纸杯蛋糕 被她抹了一脸
So Nina was a tough one?
Nina以前很坚强?
She still is.
现在也是
According to the doctors,she should have been dead months ago.
按照医生的说法 她几个月前就应该不在了
- She's a fighter. - You did a wonderful job raising her,Burton.
- 她很勇敢 - 你把她教养得很好 Burton
I would have liked to have been a part of it.
我当然希望能参与其中
But I'm glad she had you.
但幸好她有你在身边
She still does. I'll never give up on her.
现在也是 我不会放弃她
I just put all of this out of my head for so long.
我以为我已经忘记这些了
You,Nina,Kincaid.
你 Nina Kincaid
Now it's just rushing back,like a fresh wound.
现在一下子想起 就像旧伤新痕
And the enormity of what he did to all of our lives.
他所做的一切 伤害了我们所有人
God,it just makes me so angry.
让我难以抑制地愤怒
But in the end,we won.
但我们终归赢了
We beat him. Nina grew up protected from any knowledge of that terrible past.
我们赢了他 Nina长大了 不用知道这些可怕的往事
You forged a new life! You have a husband,a home.
你开始了新生活 你有丈夫 有家
Go back to it,Kate. You don't want to stir up any ghosts.
回去吧 Kate 你不应该唤醒昨日的梦魇
No.
不行
I kept quiet for too long.
我沉默了太久
You said it yourself. Nina is a fighter.
你说过 Nina很勇敢
I wanna show her I'm a fighter too.
我想她知道我也是
TEXT MESSAGE
过几小时向我报到 Logan
What's up?
怎么了
Nothing. It's about my son.
没什么 是我儿子的事
Was that his father?
是他爸爸吗
No,his father and I don't talk.
不是 他跟我已经不再联系
- Sorry. - Don't be.
- 抱歉 - 不用
It's a good thing.
这是好事
You don't have to talk about it if you don't want to.
如果你不想谈 不用勉强
I met him when I was working undercover in Mexico.
我在墨西哥当卧底时认识他
It didn't end well.
最后一拍两散
That's why I don't let my feelings interfere with business.
所以我工作时公私分明
Where do you think they took Mom?
他们把妈妈带去哪里了
They won't hurt her. They need her for the surgery.
他们不会伤害她 他们需要她去做手术
What was that all about?
究竟怎么回事
Why do they need building plans?
他们为什么要建筑图纸
I'm not sure.
我不知道
Then you should have just given them to him.
你应该给他们的
It doesn't matter what we do anyway. We can't stop them.
我们做什么都没关系 反正不能阻止他们
If you believe that,then they've already won.
如果你这么想 他们就赢了
Morgan,look at me.
Morgan 看着我
They put a bullet in me.
他们对我开枪
They took over my house. They terrorized my family.
占据了我的房子 恐吓我的家人
They threatened everything I care about in this world.
他们威胁要伤害我所重视的一切
And I'm not defeated.
但我没认输
And I'm not going to let them defeat you.
我也不会让你认输
It's not a physical battle.
这不是身体上的搏斗
It's psychological.
是心理上
So long as we're united,so long as we're together on this.
只要我们团结一致 齐心协力
We're so much stronger than they'll ever be.
我们就会比他们强大
It doesn't matter how many guns they have.
不管他们有多少把枪
Look,when this whole thing is over,
听着 当这一切结束
I don't want to say goodbye to you.
我不想跟你分开
I understand.
我明白
I feel the same way.
我也有同感
If something does happen today,I'm sorry.
如果今天有事发生 我很抱歉
I'm sorry we didn't get to spend more time together.
抱歉没能和你相处更久一点
I just don't see why your trip to St. Theodore's should be off the record,Mr. President.
我不理解 去圣奥西多教堂的行程要保密
It's a great PR story.
这是很好的公关故事
A personal prayer visit to a church built by your great-grandfather?
你去曾祖父建造的教堂进行祷告
That's a no-brainer to grab more of the Christian vote.
肯定能吸引基督徒的选票
I spend 90% of my day on empty gestures,Ted.
我每天大部分的时间都在作秀 Ted
Every once in a while,I have to do something that actually has meaning.
总有些时候 我想做些真正有意义的事
Listen. I know I'm a sinner.
我知道我有罪
I have many flaws.
我有很多污点
I make no apologies for most of them.
大部分我都并不后悔
It's simply my nature.
这就是我的本性
But I try to make my peace with God,nevertheless.
尽管如此 我仍然希望获得上帝的宽恕
And if I'm gonna have even the slimmest hope for redemption,
如果还有那么一点点可能
I can't exploit that by turning it into a photo op.
我不想把这变成又一次的政治秀
Things move fast after an assassination. You recall the chaos when Reagan was shot?
行刺后有关部门反应会很快 你记得里根那时吗
- And that was unsuccessful. - First priority.
- 那次没成功 - 最重要是
Are we absolutely certain that nothing can be traced back to us or our partners?
确保没线索追查到我们和盟友
There's no direct money trail.
没有直接金钱往来
The team we have in place are professionals.
使用的是专业团队
- They'll disappear the minute it's over. - And then?
- 行动结束马上人间蒸发 - 然后呢
NSA intercepts will be leaked to the press implicating a foreign terrorist cell.
国安局会透露给媒体 指向境外恐怖分子袭击
Money transfers will point to the involvement of a certain Middle Eastern country.
资金来源背后是一个中东国家
And the rumor mill will take it from there.
然后谣言四起
And my sister will never know the truth.
我姐姐永远不会知道真相
Not that she's ever been interested in it.
相信她也不会感兴趣
When will you move on the FBI agent and his team?
何时解决FBI探员和他的小队
As soon as the operation is confirmed.
行动成功后马上动手
Wilson. Get a GPS trace up on the phone Carlisle was using to communicate with Logan.
Wilson 追查Carlisle用来 和Logan联络的手机
I want you to start monitoring his position.
从现在起监视他的位置
- The rest of his team,too. -  Yes,sir!
- 包括他的小队成员 - 遵命
The foreign terrorist cell is a nice touch.
要好好利用恐怖分子的名目
It will set things up perfectly with the vice president.
这会为副总统扫除障碍
- When are you speaking with him? - I'm on my way now.
- 你何时和他会面 - 现在就去
We're going to discuss potential running mates for his presidential campaign.
我们要讨论下轮总统竞选伙伴
Are you confident you have his ear?
你能说服他吗
100%.
肯定的
When I'm finished,you will be at the top of his list.
等我谈完 你是他的首选
Ellen!
Ellen!
I think I got everything you asked for.
我拿到你要的东西了
- Is there anything else I can do? - No,thank you.
- 还有什么需要吗 - 没了 谢谢
You know,I really admire you.
我其实很佩服你
I do.
真的
The way you're standing by him.
你支持他的方式
The only reason I got involved with Brian is just the way he described things.
我和他一起 因为他跟我说
The way,the way things were between you two.
他对你们婚姻关系的形容
The way things were between us?
我们婚姻关系的形容?
He told me that your marriage was a lie.
他说你们的婚姻就是谎言
But clearly that's not the case.
这明显不是事实
The fact that you're doing all of this for him,even after finding out about us,I,
你在我们事发后 仍然愿意为他付出
I admire it and I'm so,so sorry,Ellen.
我很佩服 而且我感到很抱歉
- I'm so sorry. - Thank you,Samantha.
- 很抱歉 - 谢谢你 Samantha
Thank you.
谢谢
Sir,I can't track Agent Carlisle's phone.
我无法搜寻Carlisle的电话
Did you try the girl?
有没有试过那女孩
The one Logan has working for us in Duncan's group?
那个Logan的内应
Can't reach her. And there's nothing emanating from their burner phones.
没有信号 全部人的手机都是如此
They removed their batteries.
他们把电池拆掉了
Start pulling up satellite imagery and running it through facial recognition.
调看卫星影像 用面部识别系统
Find them. I don't want any loose ends.
找到他们 我不想冒险
Why are we switching burners?
为何要换手机
The one calling the shots isn't playing games.
我们的对手是狠角色
If they win today,they'll be looking to get rid of us.
他们要赢 肯定要先解决我们
How do you know?
你怎么知道
Because that's what I would do if I were in their shoes.
换了我也会这样做
- What would you pick? - Hard to say from here.
- 你怎么选 - 很难说
I think we should split up. Search all three.
或者我们分开 各自洗楼
Kincaid will be here in exactly 72 minutes.
Kincaid还有72分钟就到
That's not enough time for a proper sweep on one of these buildings.
没有足够的时间进行洗楼
We need more info.
我们要更多资料
Ellen should be calling any minute. We wait for her.
Ellen随时会来电 我们再等等
I think you're putting way too much faith in her.
我觉得你太相信她
I'm not as big a believer.
我可没那份信心
Ellen.
Ellen
I have the plans,but they're monsters,like hundreds of pages.
我拿到图纸 但很厚 有几百页
I can't make heads or tails.
我茫无头绪
Okay,Ellen. Find the Widmark Tower.
先找到威马大厦
It has all black sheeting.
外墙是黑色的
I need to know what kind of coating is on the windows.
我要知道玻璃幕墙的涂层材质
Okay,trying to find it.
好吧 我找找
Focus,Ellen.
集中注意力 Ellen
All these symbols and markings,it's like hieroglyphics.
这些符号和标记 很难看懂
What the hell does it matter what glass coating?
玻璃的涂层有啥关系
They're inside the building,they're not scaling it.
他们在大厦里面 又不是爬外墙
The coating illuminates too much of the light passing through,
涂层会影响透过的日光强度
it's going to be very hard for them to get an accurate view from that distance in the afternoon.
那么远的距离要清晰的视线 会受到下午日照影响
Okay,I found it. The glass is high efficiency-rated,triple paint,33% tint.
我找到了 是节能玻璃 三层涂层 33%的透明度
Then they're not in there. Okay Ellen,the Ormont building.
不是这栋楼 Ellen 看看欧曼大厦
From street level it looks like it gives a vantage point,but it's built on a corner lot.
能清晰看到街道 但大楼建于转角地块
Find the surveyor's report for the foundation.
找找勘测报告 查查地基资料
I need the exact angle it's built on.
我要知道地基的角度
Just look for terms like anchor bolts,and rebars,stuff like that.
看看那些术语 例如锚栓 钢筋这些
Rebar. Here it is.
钢筋 找到了
Engineer's foundation report,42.5 degrees.
报告显示地基是42.5度
42 and a half degrees.
42.5度
That angle,from the highest floors?
这个角度从最高楼层进行瞄准
Shooter would have to press his trigger against the window to get a good look down 25th. Too hard a shot.
枪手要将枪头压很低 很难
Building's out.
已经有结论了
Then that's the building.
就是那栋大楼
The De Soleil Hotel.
迪苏蕾酒店
Okay Ellen,I've gotta go. We don't have much time.
Ellen 我要挂了 时间无多
Go home,listen to the news. If anything happens...
回家 留意新闻 如果出事
I know what to do.
我知道该怎做
Good luck.
祝好运
I feel like I never get to see you anymore,Vanessa.
我还以为我不会再见到你了
You were the best staffer I ever had.
你曾是我最好的员工
A sacrifice of higher office.
是你高升的代价
You wanted to be vice president.
你想做副总统
No,I didn't. But it was clear Paul Kincaid was going to get the nomination,so I just jumped on the ticket.
我志不在此 但Kincaid已被提名 我只能顺势而为
And as I recall,you're the one who advised me to do it.
我记得当时是你建议我这样做
Politics makes strange bedfellows.
这样的结合在政治上累见不鲜
It does indeed.
确实是
Which is why I want your counsel again.
所以我再一次需要你的意见
As you might imagine,people are already beginning to strategize about the election two years from now.
有些人已经开始为2年后的选举谋划
So you've made up your mind to run when Kincaid's second term is up?
你在Kincaid任期内就决定了要参选?
- It feels awfully early to think about. - It's never too early.
- 有点太心急对吧 - 这样才能先人一步
So what about Senator Lansbury as a running mate?
你觉得和参议员Lansbury搭档怎样
His people have already approached me.
他的人有联系我
- No. - No?
- 不好 - 不好?
No senators. No representatives.
不要参议员 不要政客
Congress has a single-digit approval rating.
国会只有个位数的支持率
Anybody you pick would be poison.
你选任何人都没好结果
Since you were a governor,you can't add another person with a voting record to the ticket.
从你在州长任上开始 你就不应该和政客搭档
So where do I look?
那人选何来
You need a fresh face. Not an elected official.
你要一个新人 不是民选官员
Someone with instant name recognition,media appeal and non-partisan credentials.
这个人要耳熟能详 有媒体支持 还能被两党接受
You'll need international experience to bolster the ticket and,since you're from Texas,
需要国际经验 考虑到你是德州人
you'll need somebody who can deliver the coasts.
你需要那个人有沿海的影响力
I know exactly who you're describing.
我知道你说的是谁
I'm not describing anybody in particular,just laying out the facts.
我不是在特指某人 只是陈述事实
You were always the smartest person in the room.
你总是最聪明的
The only question is,are you interested in running?
唯一的问题是 你是否有意参选?
Kramer,remember snipers like to work in pairs.
Kramer 狙击手一般有搭档
Robert Harper will have a spotter.
Robert Harper肯定有一个观测员
Statistically,he's a white male,20s,30s.
估计他是白人 20到40岁
- Probably wearing sunglasses. - Sunglasses?
- 戴着太阳眼镜 - 太阳眼镜?
They like to protect their eyes.
他们要保护眼睛
- I got nothing. - Next floor. Let's move.
- 没发现 - 下一层 走吧
Sandrine,I think we found the spotter.
Sandrine 我想我们找到观测员了
Run room 3609,meet us at the car in five.
查查3609号房 5分钟后我们在车上碰面
Are you sure you want to go through with this?
你确定你要这样做?
I am.
是的
Okay.
好的
Well,we might as well do it properly.
或者我们可以试试
I'll go get out my video camera,and we'll tape your statement.
我会拿摄录机 录下你的供述
I never knew Nina was so much like her mother,so strong-willed.
我不知道Nina这么像你 固执己见
You know,I remember one winter,Nina wanted to stand on her sled and go down Franklin Hill.
我记得有一个冬天 Nina从法兰克林山滑雪而下
I told her she could get hurt,and she did.
我提醒过她会受伤 但她坚持要这样
Later,when she was being stitched up at the doctor's office,I thought I should be mad.
之后 当她在医院缝针时 我以为我会很生气
But I wasn't. I was just scared.
但我没有 我只是吓坏了
The thought of something happening to that girl terrified me.
可能失去她的想法让我不寒而栗
All I wanted was to keep her safe.
我会竭尽全力确保她的安全
And in that moment,I knew that there was nothing that I wouldn't do to protect her for the rest of her life.
那一刻 我知道 没有什么我是不会做的
I'm asking you,for her sake. Don't do this.
我再问一次 为了她好 别这样做
Reconsider.
你考虑下
If she is going to die,let her go without knowing the whole,ugly truth.
如果她最终会死 别让她知道这个丑陋的真相
If you like,I could talk to Nina.
如果你愿意 我会跟Nina说
We could change our arrangement.
我们的约定可以调整
You would let the two of us meet,face-to-face?
你愿意让我们两个见面?
Yes.
是的
Okay.
好的
I'll,I'll wait.
我可以等
I've kept this secret 35 years. I guess I can keep it a little longer.
我已经保守这个秘密35年 可以迟些再说出来
You have no idea how glad I am you made that decision,Katherine.
你做这个决定我很高兴
Ran the room. It was paid in cash,and the name it was registered to had no prior addresses
租房的人用的现金 名下没有地址
or matching Social Security number.
和社保号码
No doubt it's them. Keep lookout and stay in communication.
应该是他们 继续监视和保持联络
Get behind the wheel and keep the motor running.
小心行事 让引擎开着
You ready to run 36 floors?
你准备好爬36楼吗
- Time? - 39 minutes.
- 时间? - 39分钟
Let's do it twice.
够时间来回了
Quick. Quiet. Clean.
快 狠 准
Clear!
安全
That was the spotter. Where's the shooter?
这是那个观测员 枪手在哪里
- The spotter's dead. The sniper's gone. - What do you mean,gone?
- 观测员已死 枪手不见人 - 你什么意思
They aren't taking the hit from the hotel,they're just using it to get an eye on Kincaid.
他们不打算在宾馆里动手 这里只是用来监视
Hold on. Hold on.
等等
I have eyes on the sniper.
我见到那个狙击手
Robert Harper,he's with another white male.
他和另一个白人男性一起
They're both wearing electric company uniforms.
他们都穿着电力公司的制服
- Maintain surveillance. - Copy that.
- 继续监视 - 收到
- I've lost them. -  Don't move.
- 我跟丢了 - 别动
- What do ya got? - Look at this.
- 有何发现 - 看这里
The church is circled. This is their plan.
教堂是圆形的 这是他们的计划
I'm going to go through the paperwork.
我要看些资料
You keep an eye out for Kincaid. He's minutes away.
你看紧Kincaid 他很快就到了
Hey,Logan,you're a real ball of personality,aren't you?
Logan 你难道有强迫症
Sorry,Mr. President,I'm just trying to keep us on schedule.
抱歉 总统阁下 我只是希望我们准时到达
We'll be fine.
没事的
Sir,I've got a hit on Duncan Carlisle in New York.
我在纽约发现Duncan Carlisle
23rd and Broadway,15 minutes ago.
23街和百老汇 15分钟前
Son of a bitch.
妈的
He's at the go location.
他在动手的地点
He's trying to sabotage this whole thing.
他要破坏我们的行动
President's convoy located. Half click from the church.
总统的车队到了 还有30秒
Sandrine.
Sandrine
I found a public notice about roadwork being done on Broadway and 25th.
我发现一个通告 关于百老汇和25街有路面作业
An electric company van parked there wouldn't draw any suspicion.
一辆电力公司的车停在那边 不会引起注意
- Get over there now and take 'em out. - Copy.
- 马上过去解决他们 - 收到
Got a red light. It'll turn soon though.
现在红灯 但很快绿灯
They're almost at the church.
他们快到教堂了
Beta,this is Charlie. Do you have target confirmation yet?
B位 这是C位 有否看到目标?
- Can't establish comm. - Proceed as planned.
- 联系不上 - 继续行动
I'll engage the target with my scope,if necessary.
有必要的话 我会亲自确认目标
Kincaid's arriving.
Kincaid到了
Listen to me.
听我说
You have been compromised.
行动已经暴露
Stay frosty,but I want this operation carried out.
保持冷静 行动继续进行
Copy that,sir. Situation normal here. Only issue is I've lost comm with Beta.
收到 没发现异常 但我们联系不上B位
Two Canadian passports. One for you,one for your son.
2本加拿大护照 你和你的儿子
Sandrine. Sandrine!
Sandrine Sandrine!
Where are you? You need to get to them,and take the shot.
你在哪里 你要接近他们并开枪
Clear to exit vehicle,sir.
可以离开车辆了
You all right? No falling down on the job,Logan.
你没事吧 要保持警觉啊
My sole is split.
我鞋底裂开了
I think we promoted you a little too soon,son.
可能你升职升得太快了
We gotta get out of here.
我们要离开这里
Targets are down.
目标已清除
Copy that.
收到
Meet you at the rally point.
在集合点见
Nice work.
做得好
Okay,let's go,sweetie.
好了 走吧 亲爱的
We don't want to keep that driver waiting.
不能让司机等太久
It's me.
是我
It's over. We did it.
事情已结束 我们得手了
Never lost faith that you could pull it off.
我对你很有信心
See you when you get back.
等你回来再说
Looks like Aunt Leslie has the flu.
好像Leslie姑妈感冒了
So,we won't be taking that trip,after all.
我们这次去不了
Really?
是吗
But I'll make it up to you with some ice cream.
我请你吃雪糕作补偿
Come on.
来吧
Then we'll go to the park,and then to the library!
然后我们去公园和图书馆
They've been up there all day.
他们在上面呆了一整天
- So,did you... - Yes.
- 你是否... - 是的
We saved him.
我们成功了
- Mom. - Sweetheart.
- 妈 - 宝贝
- Where were you? Are you okay? - Yeah,I'm fine.
- 你去了哪里 你没事吧 - 我没事
- You helped them? - Yeah,Samantha got them for me.
- 你帮了他们? - Samantha帮我拿到了图纸
She says hi.
她向你问好
What are you guys talking about?
你们在说什么
Nothing important,sweetheart.
没什么 宝贝
I can't believe you did it.
难以想象你竟然成功了
No.
不
We did it.
我们成功了
You came through for me,Ellen.
全靠你 Ellen
Without you,I don't know what would have happened today.
没有你 我不知道结果会如何
Well,I want you to know...
我想你知道
I'm ready.
我准备好了
To kill the president?
杀死总统?
Thank you.
谢谢
Don't move!
别动
-=http://bbs.sfile2012.com=-Sync: YTET-   定风波
-------------------------- 本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用 禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负 --------------------------
Hostages Season 01 Episode 11
人质 第一季 第11集